centraldesktop.com 2015-09-19

# Privacy policy - Central Desktop

Central Desktop, Inc. ("Central Desktop") values your privacy. Central Desktop has created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our commitment to protecting your privacy and to disclose our information and privacy practices for www.centraldesktop.com and its services. We reserve the right to change this Policy and will notify you of such changes via email or our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are statisfied with any changes. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at [privacy@centraldesktop.com](mailto:privacy@centraldesktop.com).

Information We Collect  
Central Desktop collects personal information from customers who register with our services. When customers register with our services, we require a username, password, email address, first and last name, zip code, country and time zone location and billing information such as billing address and credit card number. We may also ask customers to provide additional personal information such as company name, title, education institution and other company and personal details that the customer may opt out of by not entering data when asked. We use the customer registration information to authenticate users and provide access to Central Desktop. We also use the email addresses used in the registration information to communicate with our users. From time to time, Central Desktop may contact you via email or phone to notify you of changes to its services, maintenance notifications, information about Central Desktop and promotional materials from Central Desktop. We may also send you offers on behalf of third-party partners. Users can opt out of promotional and offer emails at anytime. 

Central Desktop collects and logs aggregate user statistics and website traffic within Central Desktop. Such information includes website traffic statistics, date and time of visits, browser type used to access Central Desktop, frequency of visits and to which pages, etc. We use this information to improve the services delivered to our customers, to track and diagnose performance problems and administer the website. 

Central Desktop may disclose aggregated user statistics (for example, 50% of Central Desktop customers use the service daily) in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, affiliates and other third parties for lawful purposes. Central Desktop will never disclose such data on an individual or identifiable basis to third parties except when we must comply with laws that require such disclosure to law enforcement authorities or other government third party officials such as subpoenas.

You may deactivate your Central Desktop account and delete your personally identifiable information at any time by contacting us at [support@centraldesktop.com](mailto:support@centraldesktop.com) clearly indicating that you wish to deactivate and delete such information. 

In accordance with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA) Central Desktop does not intentionally collect personally identifiable information from nor solicit children under the age of thirteen (13) years of age.

Other than as disclosed in this Privacy Policy, at no time will Central Desktop share, rent or sell your identifiable personal information to any third parties without your express consent. 

Public Forums  
Central Desktop may create, host and provide discussion forums, message boards, chat areas, newsgroups, weblogs and other public environments to the general public and its customers. Any information disclosed in these areas is deemed public information and each user is responsible for and should exercise caution when disclosing any personal information on such forums. Central Desktop is not responsible for any action taken as a result of information presented or received in public forums, whether moderated or hosted by Central Desktop or not. If you post personal information in any of our public forums, you may receive unsolicited email and communications from other parties.

Cookies  
Central Desktop uses cookies to store and track information about your usage of our services. Cookies are encrypted and unidentifiable bits of information sent to your browser from a web server that is stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies are set each time you register, or log in or log out of Central Desktop. Cookies may be used to store your username and password so that you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit www.centraldesktop.com. We may also use cookies to gather aggregated information about user habits on our website and services. For example, we may use cookies to estimate the number of concurrent users, estimate the total number of users, measure traffic statistics and to better understand how our users are using our services. We may share this data, in its aggregate form, with advertisers, affiliates and partners who may advertise on our website and services.

Passwords  
Your Central Desktop account information, username, password and customer profile are password-protected so that you have secure access to entering and editing personal information. It is the user's responsibility to protect the security of their password. Access to Central Desktop services are protected by a unique username and password that is known by you only. Central Desktop has designed internal security processes that encrypt customer passwords to protect it from being divulged or accessed by anyone other than you. Neither Central Desktop employees nor any of its contractors can obtain or access your password. Central Desktop employees or nor any of its contractors will ask you for your password via mail, email or telephone nor any other unsolicited manner. 

Third Party Links  
When customers and users access and use Central Desktop, there may be links to websites and services operated by third parties. Central Desktop makes no representations or warranties about the policies of third party websites that are linked to Central Desktop or any of its services. Central Desktop recommends that you read the privacy policies posted by those third party websites.

Security  
Central Desktop stores its servers in a highly secure server environment with 24 X 7 monitoring, surveillance and support to prevent unauthorized access and data security. Advanced security measures including firewalls, security guards and surveillance are taken to ensure the continued service and protection of your data from natural disaster, intruders and disruptive events. 

We cannot guarantee the security of your data while it is being transmitted over the Internet and through servers that are out of our control. We strive to protect your personal information but Central Desktop cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to our website or services. Any data transmissions you make over the internet are done so at your own risk. Once we receive the data transmission, we make our best efforts to ensure its security and privacy on our systems. 

Safe Harbor  
[ We self-certify compliance with  
](https://safeharbor.export.gov/list.aspx) [ ](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor) Central Desktop complies with the US-EU Safe Harbor Framework and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Central Desktop has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view our certification page, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>

In compliance with the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles, Central Desktop commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union or Swiss citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Central Desktop at: [privacy@centraldesktop.com](mailto:privacy@centraldesktop.com)

Central Desktop has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by Central Desktop, please visit the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR web site at <http://www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints> for more information and to file a complaint.

Further Questions  
If you have further questions about our Privacy Policy, email us at [privacy@centraldesktop.com](mailto:privacy@centraldesktop.com) or via mail at Central Desktop, Inc., 87 N Raymond Ave, Floor 6, Pasadena, CA 91103 USA.

Last Updated: Nov 27, 2012
